[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110415pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 7, "question": "Wow, where do we go from here?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 8, "answer": "I don't know, but I'm hoping somewhere nice.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110415pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", ",", "RB", ":", "RB", ",", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "TO", "PRP", "JJ", "NN", ",", "RB", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "MD", ":", "IN", "PRP", "MD", ",", "RB", ",", "IN", "IN", "NN", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 29, "question": "What gave you the idea for this?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 30, "answer": "Well, it's actually very, very -- well, the idea came to me last week, actually, about a week ago, that I should -- that I should, perhaps, kind of express my happiness at this marriage in a way publicly.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110415pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "NNP", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 58, "question": "Although, I don't know Charles, you know?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 59, "answer": "Yes, I met Charles a few times.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Charles"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110415pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "WP", "VBD", "PRP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "TO", "VBG", "CC", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "JJS", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 80, "question": "George, I mean, have you had any contact with the palace in relation this song that you've done?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 81, "answer": "Only through a mutual friend who gave me -- I gave him the name of the song that I was going to sing and asked him at least to run it by them.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110415pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", ",", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "MD", "VB", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 88, "question": "You know, if they're genuinely happy for these two people, which I think a lot of people are, you know?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "CD", "NNS", ",", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 89, "answer": "George, obviously, the whole world will be watching this wedding in a couple weeks.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110415pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", ":", "RB", ",", "EX", "VBP", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 90, "question": "What do you think it means for Britain and indeed for the royal family to have such global attention?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "NNP", "CC", "RB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 91, "answer": "I think -- I think it -- well, there are two things about this wedding.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Britain"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110415pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 98, "question": "What about you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 99, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110415pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "EX", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "JJ", "RB", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "RB", "IN", "JJS", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 108, "question": "What do you think she would have made of Kate, who obviously she never got a chance to meet?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "NNP", ",", "WP", "RB", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 109, "answer": "Oh, I think she probably would have thought there was no woman good enough for her son, probably like most women.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Kate"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110415pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 110, "question": "But I think she probably would have loved her, wouldn't she?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "PRP", ",", "MD", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 111, "answer": "Yes, I think so.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110415pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 112, "question": "She seems a very sweet girl, doesn't she?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 113, "answer": "Yes, I think she seems very sweet.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110415pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 125, "question": "I mean, what kind of message would you give to them on the big day when it comes up?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "WP", "NN", "IN", "NN", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBZ", "RP", "."], "aSentId": 126, "answer": "Oh, I think they should -- I don't think they need any advice from me.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110415pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 152, "question": "Wow, where do we go from here?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 153, "answer": "I don't know, but I'm hoping somewhere nice.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["City"]}, "docId": "110415pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "CD", "WP", "VBN", "DT", "``", "NN", "''", "IN", "``", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "NNP", ".", "''"], "qSentId": 160, "question": "Oh, I do?", "question_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 161, "answer": "Yes, because you're the one who put the \"sex\" in \"Sex in the City.\"", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110415pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 173, "question": "How similar are you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 174, "answer": "Well, we look similar.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110415pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 176, "question": "In what way?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "WP", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 177, "answer": "Well, I'm sort of a serial monogamist.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110415pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 178, "question": "Are you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 179, "answer": "Yes, I am.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110415pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 185, "question": "So, how have you managed to be monogamous in an era when it's so unfashionable?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", ",", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 186, "answer": "Well, I think that I fall in love.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110415pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", ":"], "qSentId": 199, "question": "You are intimidating to men, just purely from this character, aren't you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "NNS", ",", "RB", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 200, "answer": "Well, I --", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110415pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["VBG", "."], "qSentId": 207, "question": "And how are you finding British men?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 208, "answer": "Interesting.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110415pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "NNS", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 219, "question": "So, if there are any single, good-looking guys, what kind of age range would you prefer?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", ",", "IN", "EX", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", ",", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "WP", "NN", "IN", "NN", "NN", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 220, "answer": "Well, I'm -- I like men around my age.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110415pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "DT", ",", "DT", ",", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 223, "question": "Samantha would never do that, would she?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "IN", ",", "MD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 224, "answer": "No, no, no, no.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110415pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "CD", "NNS", ",", "CD", "IN", ":", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "NN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "NN", "JJR", "IN", "NN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 226, "question": "You've written books about sex, haven't you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "NNS", "IN", "NN", ",", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 227, "answer": "Well, I've written two books, one with -- for couples about sex, and it was about communication more than anything else.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110415pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBP", "NNS", "VBG", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 238, "question": "Excuse me?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 239, "answer": "You always have guests coming in.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110415pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", ":", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "IN", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 261, "question": "What have you learned about marriage and sex and relationships over the years, do you think?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "NN", "CC", "NN", "CC", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NNS", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 262, "answer": "Well, I think it's -- it's not as easy as it looks.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110415pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "IN", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 270, "question": "Do you feel that you've had to compromise in your private life?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 271, "answer": "I felt that -- I did compromise a lot at the beginning.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110415pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "TO", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 285, "question": "Do you remain romantic about marriage?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "JJ", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 286, "answer": "Yes, I do, to an extent.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110415pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 289, "question": "Do you regret that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 290, "answer": "Some ways.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110415pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "CD", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 330, "question": "Is never a good time?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 331, "answer": "I got 20 bucks.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110415pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["JJ", "."], "qSentId": 354, "question": "How do you put on the weight?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "RP", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 355, "answer": "Fantastic.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110415pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "RB", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "CC", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 356, "question": "Eat donuts?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 357, "answer": "You can eat whatever the hell you want and you can have as much of it.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110415pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "VBG", "PRP", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 369, "question": "How many seconds did it take you to lose the weight once the movie finished?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "NNS", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "RB", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 370, "answer": "As I said to a friend of mine, it was heaven putting it on.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110415pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 378, "question": "Do you like being in your 50s?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "IN", "VBG", "IN", "PRP$", "CD", "."], "aSentId": 379, "answer": "I love it.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110415pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 380, "question": "Why?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "."], "aSentId": 381, "answer": "Because I know who I am.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110415pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 382, "question": "Who are you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 383, "answer": "I am -- I'm Kim.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110415pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "CD", "WP", "VBZ", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", ",", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "VBZ", "VBN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "CC", "VBZ", "VBN", "JJ", "CC", "JJ", "CC", "RB", "RB", "CC", "JJ", "NNS", "CC", "RB", "JJ", "CC", "RB", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 385, "question": "Who is Kim?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 386, "answer": "I think she's a woman in her 50s who's had a terrific, terrific career and has been, you know, very fulfilled in that and has been courageous and strong and lonely sometimes and crazy sometimes and very insecure and also very confident.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110415pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "VB", ",", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 413, "question": "Has that led to moments when you felt -- has it been occasionally -- you hinted at it -- being lonely, being the real woman behind Samantha?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "DT", "VBN", "TO", "NNS", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", ":", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBN", "RB", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", ":", "VBG", "RB", ",", "VBG", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 414, "answer": "Can be, yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Samantha"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110415pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 432, "question": "So he was in the navy?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 433, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110415pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 434, "question": "And he wasn't a hero?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 435, "answer": "I don't think so.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110415pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["TO", "PRP", ",", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 478, "question": "Would you like to?", "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "."], "aSentId": 479, "answer": "To me, again, it's script driven.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110415pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "WRB", "DT", "VBZ", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 494, "question": "Are you all still mates or do you all hate each other?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "DT", "RB", "VBZ", "CC", "VBP", "PRP", "DT", "JJ", "DT", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 495, "answer": "I don't know where this comes from.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110415pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "RB", "RB", "IN", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", ",", "WDT", "VBZ", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBG", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 507, "question": "If I can interview in five years time, what would you like to have happened to you in the next five years?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "CD", "NNS", "NN", ",", "WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "VB", "VBN", "TO", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "CD", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 508, "answer": "I would very much like to continue the road that I'm on, which is, you know, playing parts.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110415pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "IN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", ":", "IN", "NN", "WP", "VBZ", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "CC", "VBZ", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "JJ", "CC", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "VBG", ",", "WDT", "VBZ", "VBG", "PRP$", "NN", "POS", "NN", ",", "WDT", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 518, "question": "Where would you like to be in five years?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "VB", "IN", "CD", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 519, "answer": "ATTRALL: I'd definitely like to be in a relationship and -- with someone who gets what I do and is, you know, supportive and behind what I've always been doing, which is following my heart's desire, which is to work as an actor.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110415pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", ",", "TO", "VB", "JJ", ":", "TO", "VB", "RB", "JJ", ",", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "TO", "VB", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "RB", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "CD", ",", "RB", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", ",", "RB", "PRP", "VBD", "NN", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", ":", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBN", "NN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 529, "question": "Have you based your final decision on a suggestion that came that way?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "WDT", "VBD", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 530, "answer": "Well, no, to be perfect -- to be totally truthful, which I tend to like to be, I had this idea initially, but I thought that one, maybe they wouldn't like the idea, so I wanted something else as I =-- because I hadn't recorded anything yet.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110415pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 559, "question": "Is it a particular pressure that only the kids of famous people understand?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "WDT", "RB", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 560, "answer": "That's a completely different level.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110415pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 572, "question": "For her, who has just come into this family, just like Diana, huge pressure, isn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP$", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "RB", "IN", "NNP", ",", "JJ", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 573, "answer": "Oh, amazing.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Diana"]}}]